<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Jay</title><link>https://jaythedeveloper.tech/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Jay</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2022 21:02:41 +1200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jaythedeveloper.tech/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>First post</title><link>https://jaythedeveloper.tech/posts/first-post/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2022 21:02:41 +1200</pubDate><guid>https://jaythedeveloper.tech/posts/first-post/</guid><description>Thoughts When deciding on how my workflow for adding posts and deployment I wanted a few core things.
write posts in markdown statically render to html easy to deploy with hands off approach for the most part Since I&amp;rsquo;ve been writing a lot more Go recently, i found Hugo a good choice. It covered most of my requirements out of the box. The only hugo doesnt take care of out of the box is easy mostly hands off deploy.</description><content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="thoughts">Thoughts</h2>
<p>When deciding on how my workflow for adding posts and deployment I wanted a few core things.</p>
<ul>
<li>write posts in markdown</li>
<li>statically render to html</li>
<li>easy to deploy with hands off approach for the most part</li>
</ul>
<p>Since I&rsquo;ve been writing a lot more Go recently, i found Hugo a good choice. It covered most of my requirements out of the box.
The only hugo doesnt take care of out of the box is easy mostly hands off deploy.</p>
<p>For deployment I chose github actions and a handy github action provider <a href="https://github.com/peaceiris/actions-gh-pages">peaceiris/actions-gh-pages</a></p>
<h2 id="whats-next">Whats next</h2>
<p>I&rsquo;ve been working on a prototype for scripting part of Golang from Javascript using <a href="https://github.com/rogchap/v8go">v8go</a>. Not sure what I intend to get out of this yet or the bigger project but it sounds fun and challenging.</p>
]]></content></item></channel></rss>